dealdigs.com 2013-06-06

# DealDigs

**I. General**

DealDigs.com is owned and operated by PriceDigs LLC(DealDigs or we). DealDigs takes user privacy seriously and takes reasonable efforts to protect your privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy in order to share with you our information collection and use practices. Please read this policy carefully before sharing any personally identifiable information described below. This policy applies solely to the web site and service located at www.dealdigs.com (the Service). Since this is a growing website and because Internet technologies are constantly evolving, these guidelines are subject to change and any changes will be posted on this page. 

**II. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**  
In order to use certain portions of the Service, you may be asked for, or you may choose to provide, certain personally identifiable information such as name, email address, postal address, PayPal account and similar information. We will not collect personally identifiable information from you while you use the Service unless you voluntarily provide it to us or authorize us to collection such information. 

**III. Use of Personally Identifiable Information**  
DealDigs may use or disclose personally identifiable information to operate and manage the Service, to provide services that you have requested or respond to your other inquires or requests. In order to provide better service to our members, DealDigs might disclose your user name and total commission earned on certain pages at DealDigs.com. We may also disclose personally identifiable information in the establishment or exercise of legal rights or defense against legal claims, to comply with applicable laws or regulations, to comply with a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order or to investigate suspected fraud or a violation of the terms of the DealDigs.com User Agreement. We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party not affiliated with DealDigs.com without your consent, except in connection with the sale or merger of DealDigs.com or the division responsible for such services. 

**IV. Collection on Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
DealDigs.com does collect and track certain non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to, user IP numbers and browser type, access times, domain names, usage habits and other information which does not specifically identify any individual. 

**V. Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
We may use and disclose non-personally identifiable information for any number of reasons, including but not limited to, working with business partners and improving our Service.

**VI. Rules for Submissions and Messages**  
Responsibility for what is posted in the discussion groups or other public forums lies with each user--you alone are responsible for the content of your messages, and the consequences of any such messages. We cannot and do not review every submission a user may make. We neither endorse nor guarantee the accuracy or propriety of any submission. We do, however, reserve the right but do not assume the obligation to restrict or prohibit your use of our sites if we believe you are violating any of the terms of the agreement and to remove, edit, or relocate any submission as we see fit whether for legal or other reasons. 

**VII. Cookies and How are They Used**  
Cookies are small text files that a web site can write to your computer. We may use cookies to identify you and allow you to log in once to DealDigs and shop without having to log in again. Cookies are also used by many of our merchants to identify you as an DealDigs member. DealDigs requires its members to have cookies enabled in order to accumulate cash back rewards. DEALDIGS does not use cookies to store information such as credit card numbers, telephone numbers, or other information you provide. 

**VIII. Your Privacy with Our Merchants and Advertisers**  
DealDigs contains links to various other sites. Each of these sites has a privacy policy that may differ from that of DealDigs. The privacy practices of other websites linked to DealDigs are not covered by this privacy policy. 

The only information that may be shared between DealDigs and one of our listed merchants is information that pertains to orders in the furtherance of tracking your order and providing you with a correct reward. Order information, including order numbers and amounts, may be available to either DealDigs, the merchant, or third party affiliate program management companies for accurate tracking purposes. This information will not be released by DealDigs to other parties unless requested by you. 

DealDigs does not record any personal information passed from our members to our merchants when you are shopping through DealDigs.

**IX. Data Security**  
To ensure the security of your data, DealDigs always uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures that protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. 

**X. May I see the information you collect about me?**  
Yes! We provide our users with access to their personal account information (e.g., available cash back, transaction history) and contact information (i.e., name, address, phone number). You may access the information by logging into your account or by sending e-mail to support[at]dealdigs.com

**XI. Opt-out**  
We give you the option to remove your personally identifiable information from our list of active users completely in connection with the termination of your DealDigs.com user account. All unsubscribe or opt-out requests should be sent to us at support[at]dealdigs.com and we will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. We are not responsible for removing your personally identifiable information from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this policy. 

**XII. United States Location**  
Our Service is maintained from within the United States of America. If you are located outside of the United States, by using the Service, you authorize the export of personally identifiable information to the United States and its storage and use as specified in this policy. 

**XIII. Confidentiality and Security**  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees for whom we reasonably believe it is necessary in order to provide products or services to you. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our website.

**XIV. Effective Date**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated and effective on December 29, 2007.
